[mellow music playing]
[woman] 1931.
England and the Empire
are in the grips
of the Great Depression,
But the British aristocracy
keeps calm and carries on.
None more so
than the Davenports,
lords of Fackham Hall
for over 400 years.
The sheer grandeur
of Fackham Hall
was a testament to splendor,
and an enduring family legacy.
Its hallowed rooms
have witnessed so much.
Life and death,
laughter and tragedy,
-heartbreak and romance.
-[ringing]
But England
was a nation divided by class.
The below-stair staff
obediently served
their masters,
and prepared sumptuous feasts.
Pheasant, caviar, venison.
Whatever a guest desired,
they would supply it.
And whilst this winter
would prove particularly bleak,
the tireless work
of those staff below stairs
ensured that Lord and Lady
Davenport wanted for nothing.
They led a decadent life
of unimaginable luxury,
and barely
had to lift a finger.
[Prudence] So, finally,
one of our children is to be wed
and shall soon fly the nest.
I'm just delighted
that our beloved home
shall remain in the family.
I'm just delighted that
after so many years of courting,
she's finally
found the right cousin.
At least Poppy's got
our interests at heart,
-unlike Rose.
-Rose may yet marry.
Oh, come on, Humphrey.
Who'd want old Rose?
She's 23.
A dried-up husk of a woman.
Barren, desiccated.
A wizened old walnut
of a spinster.
Rose, darling,
would you pass the milk?
Mama, Archibald is ghastly.
It's unfair to force Poppy so.
Why can't she simply
marry for love?
Oh, how can you be
so naive, child?
Do you think that I married
your father out of love?
Because I found him attractive?
Liked his personality?
His micro penis?
No, I married him out of duty.
And we couldn't be happier.
But Mama's right, my darling.
This is about
the future of Fackham Hall.
Of our family.
We thought,
having produced four sons,
that the Davenport line
of succession was assured.
What cursed luck to lose
all four of them.
And in four completely
separate incidents.
I console myself knowing
that at least they died
doing the thing they loved.
[somber music playing]
[Rose] But does this
not make you realize
that such an archaic
system of succession,
that only recognizes male heirs
is, pardon my French...
[in French]
Rose, we must be realistic.
Your father's not going
to live forever.
Come on. Father has
the constitution of an ox.
-[choking]
-And so long as we keep
a close eye on him,
-he'll remain that way.
-How can you be so blind
to the circumstances?
Unless your sister
marries Archibald,
we will be evicted.
Forced to live
in Central London.
Then I'll find
myself a profession.
-[grunting]
-A Davenport working for money?
Are you trying to send
your father to an early grave?
All I ever think of
is Father's well-being.
Well, you evidently care less
for this family
-than your beautiful sister.
-[clattering]
Humphrey! Shield
your mouth when coughing.
My sincerest apologies,
Prudence.
My lord, ladies.
The dressing bell has been rung.
Drinks will shortly be served
in the drawing room.
-Thank you, Cyril.
-I do so hope
it will be sunny
for the wedding. Hey, Cyri.
-Mm-hm.
-What's the weather tomorrow?
Expect partly cloudy skies
in Fackham tomorrow,
with a 40 percent
chance of snow.
-[door closes]
-Do you ever worry that Cyri
is always listening in
to our conversations?
Oh, now, come.
Not this again, darling.
We've already had
to get rid of poor old Alexa.
That's true.
[lighthearted music playing]
[woman] London,
birthplace of emphysema,
child exploitation,
and a charming young
pickpocket called Eric.
National ink shortage!
Read all about it!
-You there. Here.
-National ink shortage!
Blast and botheration!
Excuse me, sir.
You dropped your wallet.
-Ah.
-[woman] Eric couldn't be
more different
from the Davenports
at Fackham Hall.
He doesn't have any land,
titles, underwear,
or vitamin D.
But what he lacks
in bone density,
he more than makes up for
in guile...
Here you go, darling.
-...charm.
-Thank you.
-[man] She's got my watch!
-...and boyish good looks.
-Come here
-I didn't steal it.
Honest to God, sir, I didn't.
Eric was amongst the thousands
of young boys orphaned
after the war.
-[Eric] Morning.
-With only his quick wits,
street smarts,
and the watchful eyes
of the Sisters of Mercy
keeping him from penury.
Morning, Sister Jude.
What can I be doing
for you today?
Nothing for me.
But this gentleman
wishes to speak with you.
And of course, our door
is always open to unknown men
with an interest
in specific children.
Yes. He seems like
just the lad for the job.
I need a letter delivered here.
To the manor house
owned by the Davenports.
An obscenely rich
family of aristocrats.
[scoffs] Fuck 'em all.
That's right.
Fackham Hall.
The most lavish manor house
in all of Shropceistershershire.
Well, I'm not doing it for
any less than five shillings.
I'll pay you a pound.
Pleasure doing
business with you, mister.
[whimsical music playing]
Good luck.
[Sister Jude] Eric.
You're the smartest child we've
ever had at this orphanage.
If only you directed your
talents down the righteous path,
you could really
make something of yourself.
"I may do some good
before I am dead."
It's Thomas Hardy.
Here's another quote for you.
"Thou shalt not steal."
[chuckles]
Ah.
Your watch, sir.
Oh.
And your trousers.
But I'm wearing my trou--
[woman]
And so begins Eric's adventure,
as he sets off to deliver
that precious letter
to Lord Davenport.
A chance to change his future.
And nothing was
going to get in his way.
Whoa.
[DJ] Shout out to Rachmaninoff.
Big up on themself.
New track from Carl Ravell
and his orchestra just dropped.
Straight-up banger. Check it.
[klaxon blares]
["So Rare" playing on radio]
[humming]
[romantic music playing]
-[brakes screech]
-[Eric grunts]
-[gasps]
-[Eric groaning softly]
[grunts]
Oh.
Are you all right?
I've never been better.
[chuckles]
Sorry I scratched your car.
Don't worry about it.
It was like that before.
I'm sorry about your bike.
Don't worry.
It was like that before.
I don't know what happened.
I think I was...
[both]
...momentarily distracted.
Yes. I only took my eyes
off the road for a second.
I think I was captivated
by the sight...
[both] ...of an incredibly
beautiful woman
with the kind
of carefree essence
that makes a man
glad to be alive!
[dreamy music playing]
Well, it was nice to meet you.
Eric.
It's Rose, actually.
It was lovely
to make your acquaintance.
And from now on, I'll pay more
attention to where I'm going.
[groans]
[lighthearted music playing]
Ms. Davenport! Ms. Davenport!
The lord and lady is wondering
where you is be, they do.
-What did you tell them?
-I spared your blushes, m'lady.
Said you were wrestling
with a tricky dump.
Oh, thank you, Patricia.
I just needed to clear my head
before watching
my darling sister, Poppy,
marry that odious Archie.
[sighs]
There. Good as new.
[baby crying]
Wonderful to see you,
Viscount Wolsey.
[Prudence] So good of you
to join us, Lord Lucan.
[Humphrey]
Welcome to our home, Lady Gaga.
Where on earth have you been?
Please don't say
reading or thinking.
As you well know,
that's men's work.
-Humpty!
-Ah!
If it isn't J.R.R. Tolkien,
the writer.
Poppy, dear old friend of mine
from Oxford, John.
Please. Call me J.R.R. Tolkien,
the writer.
[Poppy]
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Would I know
anything you've written?
I doubt it.
He's not had anything published.
Well, not yet.
But I have spent
the last 15 years
coming up
with an alphabet for orcs.
[in Orkish]
What a delightful language.
Remember, Fifi, the Davenports
are one of the most
eminent families
in the whole of England.
So, please, try not
to be too American.
Oh, please, honey.
They'll barely notice.
[whimsical music playing]
-Lord Davenport.
-[Humphrey] You remember Bert?
-Archibald's best man.
-Good to see you.
Thank you for having me.
[Bert chuckles]
[Fifi]
What a quaint little cottage.
Oh, my.
Richard, do hurry up.
Gladys, is that
really all you can carry?
[woman]
As the orphan lad approached,
he sensed
this must be Fackham Hall.
He could tell by its grandeur,
presence,
and its sign
saying "Fackham Hall."
-Excuse me, mister.
-Oh.
Ah, you're here for the position
of hall boy. Is that right?
-Actually, I just wanted to--
-There will be no negotiation.
The wage is four pounds a week.
Take it or leave it.
-I'll take it.
-Edna.
I have procured you
a new hall boy.
Heaven forfend I get a say
in who works for me.
Do let us hope he's up to it,
Cyril.
Hut. Follow me, laddie.
As hall boy, you are the
lowest-ranked member of staff.
Every afternoon,
you must polish the silverware.
Silverware is any utensil
made of silver.
Then it is dinner. Dinner is
a meal partaken in the evening.
After which you must clear
the plates from the table.
The table is an item
of furniture
with a flat top and four legs.
Finally, you must mop the floor.
The floor is the
bottom surface of a room.
A room is any space
enclosed by a number of walls.
A wall
is like a floor that's sideways.
Do you understand?
Yes, miss. I won't
disappoint you. I promise.
Get out of my sight.
Excuse me, sir.
Who do I speak to
about the hall boy job?
I'm afraid that vacancy
has been filled.
[lighthearted music playing]
[exhales]
Ms. Davenport.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Darvesh Khaled, your
father's lawyer and old friend.
Oh, yes. From the trenches.
You fought with my father.
No, we were on the same side.
Oh. Oh, Mr. Khaled,
may I introduce you
to Great Aunt Bonaparte?
A pleasure, ma'am.
Bonaparte.
Are you related to Napoleon?
Yes. He's my nephew.
Oh.
Mrs. McAllister, I've done
everything you asked me to.
-Really? Already?
-Yes, ma'am.
You've brought all the wine
up from the cellar?
Yes, ma'am.
-Taken it to the drawing room?
-Yes, ma'am.
-And closed the cellar hatch?
-[Richard whistling tune]
[clattering]
I'll do that now, ma'am.
[Richard groans]
Where is Richard?
He's supposed to be serving
the champagne.
You'll have to do it,
and not looking like that.
Get a move on.
You've got the castle,
the cathedral,
the chocolate factory.
I simply don't understand
why anyone would want
a new York.
Here's £10 to stop talking.
Now, I have a business proposal,
Mr. Davenport.
I'm expanding my fashion empire,
and I need a small pied-à-terre
in England.
How much to buy Fackham Hall?
I'm not sure you could afford it
on the wage of a seamstress.
I'll pay double its value.
And I promise
to keep its integrity.
All I'd do is add a jazz bar,
a small casino, and 30 stories.
I appreciate that this may
be the way
you conduct your business
in the Americas,
but Fackham Hall
simply isn't for sale.
[chuckles]
Well, we'll see about that.
A word of warning,
Mr. Davenport.
I have a habit
of getting what I want.
About half the size of a human.
[playful music playing]
Oh.
[indistinct chatter]
-Champagne?
-Yes, please.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Please welcome
the bride and groom to be,
Mr. Archibald Davenport
and Ms. Poppy Davenport,
his fiancée.
And first cousin.
[guests applauding]
My word, Mary, a man.
Oh, Constance.
He's so good-looking
I can barely breathe.
I can't wait till I marry a man.
It is only then that
my life will be of any worth.
Ms. Valentine, have you met
the Bechdel Sisters?
[Archibald]
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is very rare
you find someone so beautiful,
someone so intelligent,
someone that you would
move heaven and earth for.
But after years of searching,
Poppy found me.
[Poppy] I just feel so lucky.
I mean, after all,
we have so much in common.
For example, our grandparents.
-Yes.
-Yeah.
Please, enjoy the festivities.
I'm sorry. You may never host
a party like this for me.
My dear.
There are many here
who believe that marriage
validates one's existence.
I'm not among them.
I'm just so very proud of
the intelligent,
kind, and elegant young woman
you have become.
Deviled egg, ma'am?
[stifled sob]
[dreamy music playing]
Stop gawping and do your job.
[sobbing]
So, wrong side
of Mrs. McAllister on day one.
That's a record.
So, you know your music, sir.
Is that your name?
Eric Noone.
Pronounced "no one," sir.
So, which bedroom's yours then?
Oh, I never sleep.
It interferes with my duties.
Here we are.
Your quarters.
You'll be sharing with Tom,
Fred, Harry,
Richard, and Alexander.
Jammy bastard. They've put you
straight in the big room.
[Tolkien] All's well
that ends better, Humpty.
[lighthearted music playing]
Are you bride or groom, sir?
No, I'm a guest.
[vehicle approaching]
Whew!
[groans]
[Richard groaning]
[grunts]
My darling Poppy.
Now, before you embark
on this new life,
I want to give you something
that my mother gave Prudence
on our wedding day.
[tender music playing]
[music turns playful]
It's a necklace box.
Oh, wow.
Oh, Daddy, thank you.
Alexander.
Are you ready?
Mm-hm.
[organ playing "Funeral March"]
[plays "Here Comes The Bride"]
[Poppy grunting]
[Humphrey] Oh.
Daddy. [screams]
[Humphrey grunts] Oh.
Please be seated.
["Here Comes The Bride" ends]
Welcome, friends and family, and
of course, Archibald and Poppy.
Let us pray you never marry.
Let us pray.
You never marry without love.
You never love without God. God
is almighty. God is everywhere.
God is touching you all
in your private places.
God is touching you all.
In your private places,
in your darkest times,
God is there shining a light.
And today he's shining a light
for these two arseholes.
And today he's shining
a light for these two.
Our souls
are eternally in his debt. Amen.
[all] Amen.
Does anyone have a reason
why Archibald and Poppy
should not be bound together
in holy matrimony?
Speak now
or forever hold your peace.
No one? Good.
Stop.
[guests murmuring]
I know a reason why
we shouldn't marry.
I don't love him.
[guests gasp]
I love another.
I'm sorry, Archie, but I cannot
spend the rest of my life
living a lie.
[dramatic music playing]
-Lionel.
-[guests gasp]
Get up.
Pop... Poppy.
Poppy.
Now this is a fucking wedding.
[laughs]
Lionel? Lionel.
[emotional music playing]
I love you. I want us
to be together forever.
Okay. Okay.
[Poppy] Goodbye!
[exasperated yell]
[Humphrey]
Your attention, please.
[chattering]
Shh.
-Shh.
-[chatter stops]
Despite today's unpleasantness,
you must all remain
at Fackham Hall.
[Humphrey]
To spare Archibald's blushes,
I would appreciate it
if from this moment on,
nobody mentioned
this morning's... hiccup.
Specifically,
the disastrous wedding,
Archibald being humiliated
at the altar,
the enthusiasm
with which the bride fled
from her jilted fiancé.
And please, no mention
of Archibald's animalistic
wailing from the vestry,
which we all pretended
we couldn't hear.
[guest coughs]
Thank you, Lord Davenport.
That's very thoughtful of you.
Please all have
a wonderful weekend.
[lighthearted music playing]
[guests chattering]
[Patricia] I knew it about
Lionel and Poppy, I does, I did.
Oftens I saw her
sneaking back late at night.
Never not said nothing
to her ladyship. If she asked,
I said Poppy was in the woodshed
whittling a dildo.
That's quite enough
tittle-tattle from you two.
Ms. Rose
will take tea in her room.
Yes, Mrs. McAllister,
ma'am, m'lady.
[lively music playing]
You? What? Why didn't
you tell me you worked here?
Why didn't you
tell me you lived here?
This is a big house
for a chauffeur.
Yes.
I'd rather appreciate it
if you didn't tell anyone
you saw me driving Father's car.
Don't worry. You can trust me.
I'm good with secrets.
To this day, I never told a soul
about Sister Mary stealing
from the collection plate,
or Sister Jude's sex holidays
in Amsterdam,
or the time Father Jessop
tricked four choir boys into--
It's good to know
I can trust you.
You certainly can, Ms. Rose.
Excuse me for asking.
What is that you're reading?
This?
It's a tale of forbidden love.
Ah.
I'd love to borrow that
when you're done with it.
You read?
I forget who coined the phrase,
but reading brings us
to unknown friends.
-That's Balzac's.
-No, it's true.
I think it was
a French novelist.
Where shall I put your tea?
I'd best take that.
Having a gentleman
enter my private quarters
would be...
[romantic music playing]
Forbidden?
[Mrs. McAllister] Hall boy.
[Cyril]
Eric. You leave us no choice.
Your employment is terminated.
-My lady.
-I just wanted to make sure
the new hall boy
doesn't get into any trouble
as a result of my asking him
to bring me my tea.
-You asked him?
-Yes.
To give Patricia a break.
Well, I'll leave you
to your meeting.
[Rose] Oh.
I meant to ask for some sugar.
[dreamy music playing]
And you don't have to stand up
every time I enter the room.
[playful music playing]
Well, it seems
my hand is forced, laddie.
You stay.
For now.
[chuckles]
[Prudence] I truly thought
that this would be where
I would live out
the remainder of my days.
But there's little we can do.
The law is clear.
Archibald is the rightful heir
to Fackham Hall.
Why did it have to be him
of all people?
If only George hadn't died.
Or John.
Or Paul.
Or little Ringo.
Or our eldest nephew.
Humphrey.
I never dare ask Phyllis.
What actually happened
to Archibald's older brother?
-Ah, Nathaniel?
-Mm.
He went to fight the war
at a young age.
To defend the freedoms
of this great country.
[Prudence] Hm.
He was just a child.
-[high-pitched whistling]
-[gunfire]
Officer Davenport. Are you ready
to make the ultimate sacrifice?
Give those Jerries hell.
For king and country!
-[bugle playing "Charge"]
-[soldiers shouting]
I've often tried to discover
what happened to the poor boy,
but to no avail.
And now her surviving son,
jilted at the altar by our feral
little egg-brained daughter.
Even if Poppy did recant,
it seems inconceivable
that Archibald's wounded pride
would permit him
to marry her now.
What about Rose?
It's illegal
for sisters to marry.
Pity. But what if Rose
were to marry Archibald?
An intriguing proposition.
[Prudence] Hmm.
[cutlery clinking loudly]
[scraping]
Archibald? I don't know if--
[loud clinking continues]
[louder]
Archibald? I don't know if--
[loud clinking continues]
[clears throat softly]
[clinking stops]
[in normal voice] Archibald,
I don't know if I mentioned,
but Rose is very well-read.
[Archibald scoffs]
That comes as no surprise.
I mean, what else
is a woman to do
when she is without a husband?
-[Archibald laughs]
-[chuckles]
Shit just got real.
[Rose] Now that your honeymoon
has been canceled,
you shall have
more time to read.
Perhaps I could direct you
to a tome on manners.
Sick burn, bitch.
[Archibald] Maybe the next time
you find yourself in a library,
perhaps you could
seek out some texts
to explain how
a lady should behave, hm?
Maybe then you'll have a better
chance of finding a husband.
-[stomach churning]
-[Rose] Yes. It is unfortunate
to have not had a partner.
But is it not more careless
to procure one,
only to then lose her?
Wasteman just got merked.
Rose, may I speak
with you outside?
Rose, darling,
do you not see our predicament?
Thanks to your
sister's selfish behavior,
if we are
to remain in Fackham Hall,
another lady in our family
must wed Archibald.
No. You can't.
You're married to Father.
Darling. I'm talking about you.
Oh.
No! You think I would choose
to spend the rest of my life
with that pig?
No, I shall not,
and I shwill not.
-Enough. Mr. Tolkien.
-[stomach churns]
-The writer.
-Indeed.
Being contrary is the main cause
of brain degeneration in women.
Ask any male scientist.
From this moment onwards,
you must make Archibald
fall for you.
For the good of the family.
Rose.
Rose!
So sorry. It's her time of the
month, where she menstruates.
[somber music playing]
[sobs]
[sobbing]
[whistling cheerfully]
I'm so sorry.
[Rose continues sobbing]
Rose? Are you all right?
It's nothing you need
to be burdened with.
Please. It's no burden at all.
-[door creaking]
-You can tell me anything.
It will stay
strictly between us.
Mother wants me to marry
Archibald,
but I do not love him.
I see.
[sniffles]
[soft music playing]
You prefer to wait
for your Heathcliff.
You've read Wuthering Heights?
Eric, you are a rare creature.
Do you think it foolish of
a lady to listen to her heart?
I believe
that when the heart aches,
that's when
we should listen the most.
[Tolkien breaks wind]
How does anyone know
when they're in love?
-[Tolkien breaks wind]
-Maybe there's just
something in the air.
[continues breaking wind]
I should go.
[Tolkien continues
breaking wind]
[diarrhea sounds]
♪ An invite
To Buckingham Palace ♪
♪ Arrived at my home
In Belgravia ♪
♪ When meeting the king
And meeting the queen ♪
♪ One must be
On one's best behavior ♪
♪ But I went to the palace
With my willy hanging out ♪
♪ And nobody
Thought to tell me ♪
♪ They were too polite
It was hanging out all night ♪
♪ And no one stopped to tell me
That my pecker was in sight ♪
♪ I had a tiny hunch
When it dangled in the punch ♪
♪ And my johnson
Went all chilly ♪
♪ The Duke of Norwich
He thought it was a sausage ♪
♪ When he had
A little nibble on my willy ♪
♪ Silly ♪
♪ I went to the palace
With my willy hanging out ♪
♪ I don't think that
His Highness will forget me ♪
♪ The king, he saw my bell ♪
♪ But did the night go swell? ♪
♪ Well, they asked me
To the palace ♪
♪ Next week as well ♪
[guests laughing]
[Humphrey]
And look, there it is. Such wit.
[lighthearted music playing]
Your mother thought
it would be prudent
if you were
to join us for the hunt.
Perhaps Archibald
may get to know you better.
Right now, I'd gladly
swap places with the pheasant.
I've always felt that
women do not belong on hunts.
Don't be so utterly ridiculous.
Ridiculous? It's science.
Their petticoats get tangled
in the undergrowth.
Their perfumes
scare the pheasants,
and their feminine giggles,
they rust the bullets.
-[rifles cock]
-[exclaims]
Mr. Khaled, are you okay?
Yes. It's just...
the sound of guns
being primed for action.
It takes me back
to my time in the trenches.
If you don't mind my asking,
is that how you got your limp?
[explosion]
[somber music playing]
The war is over!
[laughs]
-[cheering]
-The war is over!
War's over!
-War's over!
-[yells]
-[bone cracks]
-[screaming in pain]
I'd rather not talk about it,
Ms. Davenport.
I understand.
Thank you for your service.
[horn blares]
[gunshots]
[bird screeches]
Ha!
Bloody good shot.
-[gunshot]
-Bugger it.
-[animal screeches]
Well done, Father.
-[gunshots]
-Fuck it.
Not having much luck today,
Archibald?
Just familiarizing myself
with this new weapon. [chuckles]
[gunshot]
[stag bellows]
[Bert] Bloody good shot,
old bean.
Yeah.
[Richard groaning softly]
Sir, shall I take him back
to the house and call a doctor?
No, no. Just chop his legs off
and roast him for dinner.
-[Richard groans]
-What about Richard, sir?
[Humphrey] Oh, yes. Tragic.
Without a beater,
-we must curtail the hunt.
-[groans]
-Sad day for us all.
-Father, wait.
There's a fellow
back at the house
who might be able to step up.
[lively music playing]
[gunshot]
Bugger it.
[groans]
[somber music playing]
Father. No.
[groaning]
[Humphrey] Rose.
You're the most wonderful
daughter
a father could ever
wish to have.
Tell Poppy I forgive her.
But more importantly,
tell your mother that
I... I...
shall not be
attending tea this evening.
I'll never forgive you for this.
Excuse me, Ms. Davenport.
There's no blood.
Oh.
-[chuckles] Blow me.
-[Rose chuckles]
Looks like my old pocket watch
must have saved my life.
I'm alive.
[all laughing]
-Ah!
-[Archibald]
Well, I have learned
a very valuable lesson.
Be careful where you point.
-[Rose gasps]
-[groans]
[sobbing]
[groaning]
[somber music playing]
I can see a light.
[Humphrey coughs]
I can see my sons.
John,
Paul, George, Ringo.
Let's come together.
I wanna hold your hands.
Oh, dear Prudence.
Dear, dear Prudence.
I am the walrus.
His mind's turned fevered.
[cocks rifle]
Daddy's coming, boys.
[gasps]
[grunts softly]
[lighthearted music playing]
-Ah!
-[Rose giggles]
My Bloody Mary.
-[laughing]
-[Humphrey] Of course.
Bloody Mary.
Oh, bad luck, old chap.
Ah, I really thought
you'd bagged your first kill.
[Humphrey] Bloody Mary.
Thank you
for stepping in to save Father.
Ah, well. [chuckles]
Anybody would've done the same.
But they didn't.
Rose.
I wanted to just say
sorry for shooting your father
in the heart... twice.
I'm usually
a much better marksman.
It's this faulty gun
they've given me.
It's wonky barreled.
It doesn't shoot straight.
Um... May I?
[scoffs]
Be my guest.
As I said.
[playful music playing]
[titters]
Beginner's luck.
[Humphrey]
Young man, I've been reflecting
on your swift thinking
during this morning's shoot.
You're a good sort
to have close by, Eric.
How would you like
to be my new valet?
It would be an honor, sir.
Excellent.
This calls for a cigar.
Here they are, in my secret
cigar and money drawer.
Thank you, sir.
Alexander, pen yourself a letter
with news of your demotion.
It'd be my pleasure, sir.
[indistinct chatter]
What do you keep writing
in that little book of yours?
Ideas. For my novel.
I'm always listening
out for inspiration.
Oh, darling,
have you seen my cigar cutter?
In your trousers, my precious.
Wait. Say that again.
Uh...
In your trousers, my precious?
[in Gollum-like rasp]
In your trousers.
[door opens]
Rose, I just wanted you
to know
that I was
in the library earlier,
and I chanced upon a poem
that reminded me of you.
Would you mind if I read it now?
Very well.
[delighted chuckle]
Such a beautiful poem.
-Mm.
-[Prudence]
It appears your Archie
is rather smitten with Rose.
It's nice to see him
temporarily distracted
from the Grim Reaper's
inevitable grasp.
Indeed.
I'm a lot more fun than
you probably first thought, hm?
I'm sure you are.
-Enjoy the rest of your evening.
-Uh-- [grunts]
-Cyri?
-Mm-hm.
Play dance music.
Playing dance music
on the gramophone.
[swing music playing]
Hm?
-Dance with me, Rose.
-I'd rather not.
Um... [chuckles nervously]
Don't embarrass me.
People are watching.
Let go of me.
Just dance. It's fun.
Archibald, let go of me.
Ms. Davenport
asked you to let go.
-[Archibald grunts]
-[Cyril] Oof.
-[music stops]
-[guests murmur]
Mr. Davenport,
I apologize that my face
interrupted
the flight of your hand.
-Yes.
-And I deeply regret
the behavior
of my junior colleague.
As you should.
When I inherit this place,
I'll sack the lot of you.
You impertinent morons.
-Very good, sir.
-Yes.
Eric?
[dramatic music playing]
[Mrs. McAllister] You have put
all our jobs at risk.
You are here to serve,
and serve alone.
Us lowly downstairs folk
must never become
romantically entangled
with those above stairs.
Mark my words,
it never ends well.
If we are to see out
our days at Fackham Hall,
then Rose must marry Archibald.
And you are obstructing that.
Now, for all our sakes,
first thing tomorrow,
you must pack up
your bags and leave.
[Cyril] To save any upset,
I shall simply inform
his lordship
that you have contracted rabies,
found employment elsewhere,
died,
fallen pregnant, and run away.
Now, go.
[melancholy music playing]
[door closes]
Rose. What are you doing here?
I came to find you.
What did they say?
They fired me. I leave tomorrow.
No. No, they cannot,
and they shall not.
They shwill not
and they shwell not.
I'll speak to Father.
Rose. No, it's fine.
It's done now.
-[chauffeur] Oh, no.
-This place isn't for me anyway.
-Fackham Hall?
-Yeah, fuck 'em all.
[Rose sighs]
Well...
Well, if this is to be
our last night together,
let's go somewhere.
Somewhere we can be ourselves.
Just like when we first met.
I know. Let's go to a pub.
What about the Dog & Drake?
I've driven past it many a time,
but never dared go in.
Yeah, why not.
But they're not really
the biggest fans
of you Davenports in there.
So, you can't really go in
dressed like that.
[Rose] Then I shall just
have to blend in.
[whimsical music playing]
-Evening.
[door opens]
-And stay out.
-But I'm the landlord.
After you.
[indistinct chatter]
[chatter stops]
Follow me.
[chatter resumes]
I'll have two of my usual,
please, Karl.
Who's this?
Don't you remember me?
My name is, um...
Rose...
Devon...
Port.
Rose Devonport.
Good. 'Cause for a moment,
you looked like one of them
Fackham Hall lot.
And we hate those
stuck-up bastards.
Well, I can assure you,
I'm apples and pears not.
Spoken like a true Cockney.
Thanks, Karl.
-Ow!
-Bulls-eye.
[grunting]
Come here.
Are all pubs like this?
Oh, no, no. This is a posh one.
Follow me.
Perfect. My lady.
-One...
-[slurps]
[coughs]
-Rose for the lady?
-Thank you, but I have
a beautiful rose
of my very own right here.
[giggles]
Suit yourself, love.
It's so thrilling
being here with you.
No more pretending, no more
holding back my feelings.
I can be myself.
Tell me your dreams.
Well, I have this dream
where my penis falls off,
but I can't go to the doctor
because I'm late for school.
Same.
-Really?
-[chuckles]
Do you have any other dreams?
I dream of one day escaping
to the most
romantic place on earth.
The city of love.
The city of art.
The city of poets.
Blackpool.
Wow.
Maybe we could go there
one day. Together.
Yes.
[plays lively flourish]
Oh, no. It's a Cockney knees-up.
Join in. You'll definitely
all know the words
'cause we're all genuine
Cockneys here, aren't we?
[all] Yeah!
Just follow along,
you'll be all right.
[singing]
[patrons cheering]
[clapping in rhythm]
[coughing]
[music stops]
Oh, well, he made it to seven.
To London's oldest
ever chimney sweep.
[all] Yeah!
[continues playing
lively flourish]
[singing]
[music and singing stop]
Uh...
Capital city?
[all cheering]
For a minute there,
I thought she didn't know it.
[laughs]
Yeah!
[tender music playing]
You cold?
[woman] But unbeknownst
to our star-crossed lovers,
life at Fackham Hall was about
to take a turn for the worse.
Especially for Lord Davenport.
[dramatic music playing]
Humphrey, open a window.
Something smells ghastly
in here.
Humphrey.
[screams]
[cat yowls]
[somber music playing]
[elegant music playing]
[knocking on door]
Inspector Robert Watt.
I'm here regarding the murder
of Lord Davenport.
I'm afraid you're too late.
Someone's already done it.
But come in anyway.
Follow me.
[Watt] Hmm.
Uh-huh.
Oh, yeah.
Cyril, who was the last person
to see Lord Davenport alive?
The murderer.
Just as I thought.
Now, would you be so kind
as to pour me a glass
of that whiskey?
Certainly.
Wait. This is poison.
Precisely.
So, Lord Davenport was poisoned.
Not necessarily.
-Do you see this?
-Yes.
Tiny holes in the lapel.
Whoever did this had access to
some form of caustic chemical.
And do you smell that?
[sniffs]
Whew, yes.
An intense sulfurous odor
that stings the eyes.
[thud]
My apologies.
That happens when I crouch.
Oh.
Specks of blood.
Hm.
What did you wish to
speak to us about, Mr. Khaled?
No, no, no, no.
Please, call me Darvesh.
As you know, Humphrey entrusted
his affairs to my legal firm.
He may have been my client,
but more than that,
he was a dear friend
and an honorable soldier.
I just wish I could have been
there last night
to save his life
just as he saved mine
in the war.
-[poignant music playing]
-[soldiers shouting]
-Incoming!
-[gunfire]
[both grunting]
You really should
get that mole checked out.
Poppy.
I'm so glad to see you.
[Poppy] Hello, Mother.
Poppy.
Am I welcome here?
Of course you are. Fackham Hall
will always be your home.
Fackham Hall
is no longer your home.
On the death of the lord,
the title and estate
passed to the next male heir.
Therefore, Archibald Davenport
is now lord of Fackham.
But we're aristocracy.
Surely laws don't apply to us.
Is there nothing
that can be done?
The only respite I can offer is
the title cannot
legally pass to Archibald
until the investigation into
Humphrey's murder is concluded.
So, if, say, Rose were to marry
Archibald before that?
[chuckles]
Then you can all remain here.
[melancholy music playing]
The inspector would like your
presence in the drawing room.
What if we haven't got him
a present?
Oh, very well.
[Khaled clears throat]
Poppy, what should I do?
I don't want our family
to be evicted.
But what is a life
devoid of love?
My dear Rose.
You know, I too
was once blinded by love.
In those early
blooms of passion,
I didn't care a jot that Lionel
wasn't an aristocrat,
that he had no money,
that he didn't wash.
I didn't care
that he wasn't handsome
or kind, or monogamous,
or allowed near schools.
But if I were to have
my time again,
maybe, just maybe
I wouldn't have
given all of this up for Lionel.
It appears you no longer
need to pack, young Eric.
The inspector says
no one can leave.
Apparently,
we are all suspects now.
[Fifi] I'm sorry,
I don't finance novels.
[Cyril] Well, Lord Davenport
shouldn't be on your list
because he's dead.
But otherwise, everyone's here.
Thank you, Cyril.
I shall erase him.
Good. [clears throat]
My lady, esteemed guests.
This is Inspector Watt.
Well, I don't know.
Inspector Phillips?
-Hole.
-Wan-Bissaka.
-[Fifi] Esposito.
-[Rose] Drew.
-[Phyllis] Gadget?
-Aragorn.
-Spector.
-[Cyril] No, no.
His surname is Watt.
I don't know. Inspector Deck?
-Inspector Thoroughly.
-Clouseau.
-Two-Bissaka.
-[Fifi] Bush.
-[Phyllis] Branagh.
-Spectacles.
-Treebeard.
-[Cyril] No, no, no, no.
His surname is Watt,
spelled W-A-T-T.
A-ha. I see. "Watt" is his name.
-Robert.
-Robert what?
-[Cyril] Exactly.
-Then what's his surname?
-Yes.
-I'm so sorry,
but I still don't understand.
What don't you understand?
No, I understand perfectly.
Now...
After examining the evidence,
I believe Lord Davenport's
murderer
to be somebody in this room.
[all gasp]
What reason would anyone here
have for killing my husband?
Maybe they were fed up of
waiting to inherit this mansion.
[scoffs]
[Watt]
Or angry at being demoted.
Or humiliated
after their attempts to buy
the hall were rebuffed.
Or maybe
it's a failed police inspector
desperate for a case to solve.
I mean, where was I
on the night of the murder?
-[Fifi] Exactly.
-[Phyllis] Indeed.
Be warned. I shall be
watching you all very closely.
And if there's anything
out of the ordinary,
anything at all,
you can be damn sure
I'll notice it.
[dramatic music playing]
[bell tolling]
[solemn music playing]
[laughing]
Truly a beautiful service.
Oh, thank you.
Although in hindsight,
I probably should
have attended the funeral.
Truly beautiful ceremony.
It was just as Humphrey wanted.
Never did like the idea
of a burial.
Always thought the alternative
was somehow more dignified.
Indeed.
[indistinct,
intense talking nearby]
Excuse me.
You do it, and you do it now.
Emotions running high?
Not at all.
Just a minor disagreement.
Before you jump to conclusions,
our discussion
was not about Humphrey.
It was about Rose.
Mother is keen for us to marry.
I'd wager your mother
can't wait to move in here
and leave your crumbling
family home.
Hm. Who told you
our house was falling apart?
-You just did.
-[scoffs]
Come on.
If you want a real suspect,
try looking into
that orphan boy, hm?
He viciously
assaulted me last night.
Who's to say that his
violent tendencies ended there?
I'm so sorry.
I can't imagine
what you're going through.
It's so hard.
Thanks. I've been working out.
Anyone could see just how
proud your father was of you.
May I have a word
with you... inside?
[Archibald] Hm?
[suspenseful music playing]
Rose, you are an angel
sent in my hour of need.
The first flower of spring.
But more than that,
you are the most beautiful
Davenport sister
currently available.
-Archibald.
-No, I promise to listen to you.
-But, I--
-I will never,
ever interrupt you.
Please make me
the happiest man alive.
Rose, will you marry me?
Mm-hm?
I...
[somber music playing]
[Archibald] Rose?
I need time to think about it.
Of course.
I completely understand.
Take as much time as you need.
-Now?
-Still undecided.
Okay.
Well, you have till Friday.
Otherwise, I will propose
to one of the Bechdel sisters.
I don't care which one.
[dramatic music playing]
A man looked at us.
[melodramatic gasp]
[thud]
[dramatic music continues]
Dear Lord,
I pray for your forgiveness.
The woman I love is being made
to marry a man she hates.
And I felt powerless
to stop it.
So, I strayed from
the righteous path.
That money, he didn't earn it.
So, Lord, please forgive me.
And I promise that after this,
I will never, ever steal again.
Amen.
[dramatic music continues]
If you've been murdered
by a candlestick, dial seven.
by a rope...
[soft tapping on window]
What?
[tapping continues]
Rose, you don't
have to marry Archibald.
What do you mean?
I've withdrawn my savings.
Let's run away together.
-Let's start a new life.
-In Blackpool.
Blackpool, Clacton, Skegness.
The world is our oyster.
Skegness. That sounds
rather nice. Where's that?
I don't know.
But we can find out.
Together.
But we have to go now.
[dramatic music playing]
I can't believe
we're doing this.
Well, it's happening.
And no one can stop us.
[siren wailing]
What on God's flat earth
is going on?
I received an anonymous tip-off
from Mrs. McAllister
that these two were absconding
with money stolen
from Lord Davenport.
Look, Rose
had nothing to do with it.
I lied.
I said the money was mine.
[Prudence]
I told you, Cyril, didn't I?
-Oh, yes, yes, you did, yes.
-I told you one of the staff
would fall
for our eldest daughter,
find an envelope full of
Humphrey's money in a drawer,
steal it, coax Rose out by
throwing stones at her window,
and attempt to drive away,
only to be thwarted
by a police investigator
who has trouble holding things.
So, you didn't
get everything right.
[Watt breaks wind]
Oh.
So, what else are you hiding,
young man?
Nothing. Nothing. I swear.
[Prudence gasps]
[tense music playing]
No. None of this is mine.
Your roommates told me
you were home late
on the night
of Lord Davenport's murder.
So, where were you,
and who were you with?
Well, if he won't tell you,
I will.
-That night we were--
-Completely separate.
No. No, we were in--
Our nightwear, in our own rooms
because it was bedtime.
[Rose] No.
-We were together in the pub...
-...licly-held view
that ladies and staff
should never mix.
[muttering]
Well, Eric Noone.
In that case,
I am arresting you for murder.
And in that case
are my toothbrush and pajamas.
[thunder rumbles]
Just tell them you were with me.
I can't.
Why?
You're a lady. You've got
your whole life ahead of you.
If I damage your reputation,
then that life is over.
I'm a no one. No ones
go to prison all the time.
[thunder rumbles]
Eric.
I know that one day,
we will be together again.
But in those intervening years,
as I await
that wonderful moment,
I swear to you
with all my heart,
I will arrange for the gardener
to have an eye test.
[dramatic music playing]
[Gladys] I don't get it.
Eric never seemed like
the murdering sort.
He wouldn't have stopped
until he'd taken all our jobs.
Aren't I right, Mom?
I mean, Mrs. McAllister.
[playful music playing]
Sometimes I accidentally
call people "Mom."
Do it all the time.
Don't I, Mrs. Mom?
Mrs. McAllimom.
Mrs. McAllimommy.
McAllister.
Mrs. McAllister.
[wailing]
Poppy?
[continues wailing]
Poppy, whatever's the matter?
Lionel left. He said
he doesn't love me anymore.
He probably just said that
in the heat of the moment.
He said, "This is not
a heat-of-the-moment thing.
I've been thinking
about this for days."
Well, just give him some
time to calm down.
He said, "I don't need time
to calm down.
I'm actually really calm,
and this is the calmest
I've ever been."
Well, it's his loss.
Then he said,
"I stole all of your jewelry
and I sold it.
So, it's very much a win for me
and your loss."
[sobbing]
I fear that,
as you both inexplicably
refuse to wed a member
of your own family,
we shall all soon be homeless.
[continues sobbing]
Oh, ladies.
I have lived through
many difficult times.
Those times
have taught me a lot.
So, I can honestly say
you are a bunch of whiny cun...
[car horn blares]
Sorry.
[continues sobbing]
[melancholy music playing]
Dearest Eric.
My heart is broken.
I didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
The image of you
reading this letter
alone in your prison cell
is something I cannot bear.
Every night when I fall asleep,
I relive the moment
you saved me from ignominy,
and I scream.
Every morning,
I awaken in tears
and reach for a handkerchief
to give my eyes a dab.
I hope that one day
you can forgive me
for what I'm about to do.
I shall accept
Archibald's proposal.
These will be the last words
you receive from me.
All my love, Rose.
XOXOXOX.
[sniffs]
[indistinct chatter]
[Rose clears throat]
Ah, Rose. How did you sleep?
By lying on my bed
and closing my eyes.
Oh, right.
-Archibald?
-Yes.
I have something to say.
Two days ago,
you asked me to marry you.
And since that moment,
I've thought of little else.
This morning,
I've come to a firm conclusion.
My answer is...
[intriguing,
playful music playing]
[gags softly]
[whispers] Yes.
Hm.
She said yes.
-[guests cheering]
-[Archibald laughs]
Huzzah!
[chuckling]
[clattering]
[indistinct shouting]
[cell door slams]
I know that look.
Your heart's been broken.
I, too, have tasted
true love and lost it.
"You shouldn't be together,"
they said.
"You're from
two different worlds."
So, we ran away.
But we got caught.
It's like we've lived
the same lives.
Here.
This is Mildred.
Isn't she beautiful?
-Mm.
-Do you have a photo
of your love?
Um...
I nicked one before I left.
I was meant to give this
to Lord Davenport.
Well, open it.
What are they gonna do?
Lock you up? [chuckles]
"Yours sincerely,
Austin Blaine."
What could it mean?
Try the other side.
[Eric] Ah.
"Dear Lord Davenport.
Years ago, you tasked me
with investigating
what happened to your nephew,
Nathaniel, in the war.
After months
of backbreaking work
and ingenious sleuthing
on my part,
I finally managed to unearth
Nathaniel's army records,
and discovered
that on returning from service,
he was mistaken for a war
orphan and raised by nuns.
[pensive music playing]
"With no clue
as to his real identity,
the sisters renamed him.
Nevertheless,
I tracked him down.
Nathaniel Davenport,
eldest son of
your deceased brother, William,
now goes by the name
of Eric Noone.
The very boy delivering
this letter to you.
Dope reveal, right?
The dope reveal will cost you
an extra farthing.
Yours sincerely,
Austin Blaine."
Blimey. I can't believe it.
I'm only sharing a cell
with the aristocracy.
What difference
does it make now?
I'm stuck here in this prison,
and the love of my life
is about to marry Archibald.
Yeah. Your brother.
-What?
-Your brother.
If you're Lord Davenport's
long-lost nephew,
that makes you
Archibald's older brother.
Which means...?
I'm the rightful heir
to Fackham Hall.
You had sex with your cousin.
Guard. I'm the rightful heir
to Fackham Hall.
Really? That's amazing. Then
I'll let you out immediately.
-You will?
-Of course I fucking won't.
[playful music playing]
[man whistling tune]
I can't let Rose ruin her life
by marrying
that horrible bastard.
I've got to get out of here.
Well, you could
always tunnel out.
If only you had
something to dig with.
Oi...
[dramatic music playing]
[both chuckling]
[laughing]
Yes.
[dramatic music continues]
[laughs]
[bells ringing joyfully]
I hope Rose isn't going
to disappoint us like Poppy did.
-She won't.
-Well, you say that.
But my William married me
and then he died.
Just as Humphrey
married you and died.
And one day, Rose will die.
We're just particles heading
towards a cold, dark entropy.
But it's a lovely day for it.
[lighthearted music playing]
Fellas. I've brought
a cake to celebrate
30 years without any escapes.
[creaking]
[Eric groans]
All right?
[lighthearted music continues]
[groans]
[both grunting]
[officer] Oi.
-[Eric grunts]
-Nice try, son.
Let's get you back
to your cell, eh?
[grunts]
-In here, pass them through.
-Here, 'gis it.
[lighthearted music continues]
Hang on.
I know you.
You're that lad from the pub
with the bird
who's definitely a Cockney.
What are you doing in here?
They think I murdered
Lord Davenport that night.
No, impossible. You was with me.
Go on. Quick.
[lighthearted music continues]
He went that way.
[organ playing hymn]
♪ War and death and poverty ♪
♪ Measles, violent brawls ♪
♪ Cancer and dictatorships ♪
♪ The Lord God made them all ♪
[hymn ends]
You may be seated.
God is with you all,
and Jesus is gay.
and Jesus is.
Gay as we are
on this joyous day,
we must take a moment
to offer thanks.
Clergymen such as myself
are given a power.
And that power
is to prey on children.
And that power is to pray.
On children,
God bestows a future.
On man, God bestows wisdom,
for God is strong and mighty,
and made us all hard.
And made us all.
Hard as life may be,
he is there to show the way.
[dramatic music playing]
Somebody stop that fugitive.
I'm innocent.
And now I know the truth.
The truth? But how?
I'm going to the church.
I'm gonna tell them everything.
Stop. Stop.
What's up, darling?
[man grunts]
Helmet.
[revving]
[dramatic music continues]
[motorbike approaching]
[Mrs. McAllister] Get back here.
[indistinct chatter]
[woman] Hey!
Move.
[both grunting]
[salesman] Trampolines.
Get your trampolines.
Crash mats. Get your crash mats.
[onlooker] Didn't think
he was gonna make that.
-[man groans]
-[Mrs. McAllister groans]
[seller] Crushed my clementines.
Does anyone have a reason
why Archibald and Rose should...
[dramatic music continues]
Move.
[man groans]
[grunts]
In sickness and in health.
Until death do us part.
[Archibald]
Now, Rose, repeat after me.
-I, Rose Davenport.
I, Rose Davenport.
Hello.
Why are you doing this?
I can't have you telling
everyone I killed Humphrey.
What? What?
Humphrey and I
kept our secret this long,
and I'll be damned
if I'm gonna let you
tell all of them
about our affair.
Or what I did to him.
-What you did to him?
-It was an accident.
Just another one
of our wee tiffs.
[Mrs. McAllister] That boy Eric
is ruining all of our lives.
First, he injures Richard
and steals his duties.
And then you give
him Alexander's job.
It's not fair on the boys,
Humph.
[loudly] They are our sons!
Keep your damn voice down.
[in normal voice] That's all
you want from me, isn't it?
To keep quiet and carry on.
Get rid of him.
Or I'll tell everyone
about our affair.
Edna.
My darling.
Come now.
No.
Be sensible.
-No.
-[groaning]
-[whimpers]
-Humphrey?
-[gasps]
-[groaning]
Oh, my God.
Don't... Don't touch it.
-I'll call for help.
-What? No time.
Shoot it out.
Yes, yes.
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
-It didn't work.
-It's okay.
We just need to get
the bullets out. Grab that acid.
We can dissolve them.
Wait, wait.
I just need to steady my nerve.
[grunts]
Ah!
Okay. Do it.
-[acid sizzling]
-[screams]
-It's burning.
-You're still bleeding.
Quick. You've got to stop
the blood leaving my brain.
Use your belt as a tourniquet
on my neck.
[Humphrey groaning]
-[choking]
-[grunts]
It's not working.
[yelling]
[both yelling]
[owl hoots]
[dramatic music playing]
[sobbing]
That's when
I decided to frame you.
Nobody cares if a wee
orphan boy ends up in jail.
Or dead.
Watt?
I'm not gonna say all again.
No.
Inspector Watt.
Did you hear that?
I certainly did.
Madam, you are under arrest.
For manslaughter.
-[handcuffs clatter]
-Ah.
In sickness and in health.
Until death do us part.
Stop the wedding.
[guest gasp]
What the fuck is going on?
What the fuck is going on? Eric?
You don't have
to marry Archibald.
Get this murderous scum
out of here.
He's not the murderer.
[guests gasp]
It was Mrs. McAllister.
And Archibald is not the
rightful heir to Fackham Hall.
What?
I have a letter here
that explains everything.
Mom.
It's me. Nathaniel.
[guests gasp]
My son. You're alive.
So, does that mean...?
That we can be together.
And you and your family
can live in Fackham Hall
for the rest of your lives.
Well, I've always rather liked
being the only
-child.
-No.
[gunshot]
[guests clamoring]
You truly are a terrible shot.
-Well, I...
-You're nicked.
-What?
-It's Inspector Watt to you.
-Get your dirty hands off me.
-Would it be possible
to pick up where we left off?
Except with this gentleman?
Yes. Yes, well, where were we?
-Let go of me, I say.
-Rose Davenport,
do you take Eric Noone,
AKA Nathaniel Davenport,
-to be your husband?
-I do.
And do you, Eric Noone,
AKA Nathaniel Davenport,
take Rose Davenport
-to be your wife?
-I do.
Well, then,
I pronounce you man and wife.
You may kiss the choirboys.
[soft lighthearted music
playing]
You may kiss. The choirboys
will now sing Ave Maria.
Fackham Hall is saved.
Bravo.
[both chuckle]
I don't think we've met.
J.R.R. Tolkien, the writer.
Oh. Bill. Bill Bobaggins.
What a wonderful name.
Bilbo Baggins.
And this is the donkey
I'm fucking.
Well, I've written it down now.
[woman] Love.
It can transcend boundaries.
There is nothing more powerful.
Other than, in this case,
birthright.
You may wonder how I was privy
to so much of what
took place in Fackham Hall...
-Move a little to your right.
-...that fateful week.
-Excellent.
-That, dear friends,
-is because I was there.
-Three, two, one...
-Fackham Hall.
-And who am I? I'm no one.
Rose Davenport Noone.
[all] Fackham Hall.
[Rose] And this...
-[all gasp]
-...is my story.
[lively music playing]
[lively music continues]
[lighthearted music playing]
[music fades out]
[somber music playing]
[elegant music playing]
[pensive music playing]
[delicate music playing]
[lively music playing]
[music ends]